

Eyup S. ERGIN

Cyber Threat Intelligence Analyst & Golang Dev.

Website: www.ergin.dev Mail: ergindev@gmail.com Phone: +90 (545) 458 7596

Github: <u>@EyupErgin</u> Twitter: <u>@ErginDev</u>

LinkedIn: <u>Eyup Sukru Ergin</u>

"With my researcher and innovative spirit, I am an intelligence analyst who has been researching Threat Intelligence since 2018, working on cyber warfare methodologies and developing open-source projects for Threat Intel. In nutshell, I am Eyup. I am 18 years old."

For more information about me, please click!

Professional Experience

Founder

VxThreat T. Intelligence Project
Jan 2022 - Present | <u>www.vxthreat.com</u>

I launched VxThreat, an Cyber Intelligence platform, in January 2022. The project includes many Threat Intelligence services, including the monitoring of Ransomware Groups, regular monitoring of Malware Types.

Cyber Threat Intelligence Analyst

Seccops Cyber Security Technologies
Jul 2021 - Feb 2022 | www.seccops.com

I was a member of the Cyberthint team at Seccops Cyber Security, where I worked in the Threat Intelligence position for about 1 year. During my tenure with the team, I conducted lengthy and detailed work on Log Files Analysis, Malware Analysis, Corporate Reports, and Annual reports, as well as the Ransomware and APT groups.

Intern IT Asistant

OMMER Machinery Construction
Apr 2021 - Aug 2021 | <u>www.ommermakine.com</u>

During my compulsory internship period, I had the opportunity to work as an Intern IT Assistant at OMMER Makine. During this time, I gained a lot of experience in network systems.

Professional Qualifications

Computer Aided Machine Technician

Afyonkarahisar Voc. and Tech. Anatolian High School (2022)

Certificates

MITRE ATT&CK Defender™:

- ATT&CK® Cyber T. Intel. Certification
- ATT&CK® Threat Intelligence Badge Training

Rapid7™:

• Threat Intelligence with Insight-IDR

Cybrary™:

- Application of the MITRE ATT&CK Framework
- Advanced Cyber Threat Intelligence
- Malware Threats Intelligence & Analysis
- Open Source Intelligence Analysis

To reach more, About & LinkedIn

Languages

English B1/B2:

Reading: 8/10Writing: 8/10

Listening: 7/10Speaking: 4/10



Eyup S. ERGIN

Cyber Threat Intelligence Analyst & Golang Dev.

Technical Skills & Tools

Software Developing:

- C
- Golang

Cyber Threat Intelligence:

- Threat Hunting
- Military Intelligence
- APT Tracking
- Ransomware Attack Monitoring
- OSINT/CYBINT/DNINT
- Log Analyzing
- Malware Analyzing
- DFIR

Technical Skills & Tools

OS:

• GNU/Linux

Network:

- PCAP File Analyzing
- Network Vuln. Scanning
- Firewalls
- Encryption Algorithms

References

Ismail SAYGILI

Seccops | Co-Founder & General Manager ismail.saygili@seccops.com

Hüseyin MERT

Monopayments | CEO huseyin@monopayments.com